First hunt. Last chance.
Predator: Badlands is a action, science fiction,
adventure film directed by Dan Trachtenberg.
Cast out from his clan, a young Predator finds an unlikely ally in a damaged android and
embarks on a treacherous journey in search of the ultimate adversary.
Thia / Tessa, played by Elle Fanning.
Dek / Father, played by Dimitrius Schuster-Koloamatangi.
Bud, played by Ravi Narayan.
Kwei (Suit), played by Michael Homick.
Kwei (voice), played by Stefan Grube.
Father (Suit), played by Reuben De Jong.
Predator: Badlands is a 2025 American science fiction action film directed by Dan
Trachtenberg and written by Patrick Aison from a story by Trachtenberg and Aison.
The seventh installment in the Predator franchise, and set after the events of The Predator
(2018), it stars Elle Fanning and Dimitrius Schuster-Koloamatangi in leading roles.
The story follows Dek, a young exiled Yautja, who crash-lands on a hostile planet and must prove himself worthy of the hunt
by killing an apex predator, leading him to form an alliance with Thia, a Weyland-Yutani Corporation android.
Predator: Badlands premiered at the TCL Chinese Theatre on November 3, 2025, and was
released in the United States on November 7, by 20th Century Studios.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics
and grossed over $184 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of survival, outcast, alien planet, team up, admiring.
The tone is thought_provoking.